export default Questions= [
  {
    question: 'Q1 : What Does HTML Stand For?',
    options: [
      'Hyper Text Markup Language',
      'Hypers Tool Markup Language',
      'Home Tool Markup Language',
      'How Text Markup Language',
    ],
    ans: 'Hyper Text Markup Language',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q2 : Who is making the Web standards?',
    options: [
      'Mozilla',
      'The World Wide Web Consortium',
      'Google',
      'Microsoft',
    ],
    ans: 'The World Wide Web Consortium',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q3 : What is the latest version of HTML?',
    options: [
      'HTML4',
      'XHTML',
      'HTML5',
      'HTML6',
    ],
    ans: 'HTML5',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q4 : What is the correct HTML element for the largest heading?',
    options: [
      '<h6>',
      '<h1>',
      '<heading>',
      '<head>',
    ],
    ans: '<h1>',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q5 : Which HTML attribute is used to define inline styles?',
    options: [
      'class',
      'font',
      'style',
      'styles',
    ],
    ans: 'style',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q6 : Which HTML tag is used to define an internal style sheet?',
    options: [
      '<style>',
      '<script>',
      '<head>',
      '<link>',
    ],
    ans: '<style>',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q7 : What is the correct HTML for adding a background color to a web page?',
    options: [
      '<body bg="yellow">',
      '<body style="background-color: yellow;">',
      '<background>yellow</background>',
      '<bgcolor=yellow>',
    ],
    ans: '<body style="background-color: yellow;">',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q8 : What is the correct HTML for making a text input field required?',
    options: [
      '<input type="text" required>',
      '<input type="text" validate>',
      '<input type="text" required="true">',
      '<input type="text" necessary>',
    ],
    ans: '<input type="text" required>',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q9 : What is the correct HTML for creating a hyperlink?',
    options: [
      '<a href="http://www.example.com">Example</a>',
      '<hyperlink>http://www.example.com</hyperlink>',
      '<link>http://www.example.com</link>',
      '<url>http://www.example.com</url>',
    ],
    ans: '<a href="http://www.example.com">Example</a>',
  },
  {
    question: 'Q10 : What is the correct HTML for inserting an image?',
    options: [
      '<img href="image.gif" alt="MyImage">',
      '<image src="image.gif" alt="MyImage">',
      '<img src="image.gif" alt="MyImage">',
      '<picture href="image.gif" alt="MyImage">',
    ],
    ans: '<img src="image.gif" alt="MyImage">',
  },
];
// export default Questions= [
//   {
//     question: 'Q1: Who is the current captain of the Indian cricket team?',
//     options: [
//       'Virat Kohli',
//       'Rohit Sharma',
//       'MS Dhoni',
//       'Ravindra Jadeja'
//     ],
//     ans: 'Virat Kohli'
//   },
//   {
//     question: 'Q2: Which country won the first Cricket World Cup in 1975?',
//     options: [
//       'Australia',
//       'West Indies',
//       'India',
//       'England'
//     ],
//     ans: 'West Indies'
//   },
//   {
//     question: 'Q3: Who is the leading run-scorer in international cricket?',
//     options: [
//       'Sachin Tendulkar',
//       'Ricky Ponting',
//       'Virat Kohli',
//       'Brian Lara'
//     ],
//     ans: 'Sachin Tendulkar'
//   },
//   {
//     question: 'Q4: Which bowler has taken the most wickets in Test cricket?',
//     options: [
//       'Muttiah Muralitharan',
//       'Shane Warne',
//       'Anil Kumble',
//       'Glenn McGrath'
//     ],
//     ans: 'Muttiah Muralitharan'
//   },
//   {
//     question: 'Q5: Who has hit the most sixes in international cricket?',
//     options: [
//       'Chris Gayle',
//       'Shahid Afridi',
//       'Brendon McCullum',
//       'Rohit Sharma'
//     ],
//     ans: 'Chris Gayle'
//   },
//   {
//     question: 'Q6: Who was the captain of the Australian cricket team that won three consecutive World Cups?',
//     options: [
//       'Ricky Ponting',
//       'Steve Waugh',
//       'Mark Taylor',
//       'Allan Border'
//     ],
//     ans: 'Ricky Ponting'
//   },
//   {
//     question: 'Q7: Who has taken the most catches in international cricket?',
//     options: [
//       'Jacques Kallis',
//       'Ricky Ponting',
//       'Mahela Jayawardene',
//       'Mark Waugh'
//     ],
//     ans: 'Ricky Ponting'
//   },
//   {
//     question: 'Q8: Which team has won the most number of ICC World Cups?',
//     options: [
//       'India',
//       'Australia',
//       'West Indies',
//       'Pakistan'
//     ],
//     ans: 'Australia'
//   },
//   {
//     question: 'Q9: Who was the first player to score a double century in ODI cricket?',
//     options: [
//       'Sachin Tendulkar',
//       'Chris Gayle',
//       'Virender Sehwag',
//       'Martin Guptill'
//     ],
//     ans: 'Sachin Tendulkar'
//   },
//   {
//     question: 'Q10: Who has scored the highest individual score in Test cricket?',
//     options: [
//       'Brian Lara',
//       'Matthew Hayden',
//       'Virender Sehwag',
//       'Gary Kirsten'
//     ],
//     ans: 'Brian Lara'
//   },
// ]